maruthitalkies.com 2016-05-06

# Privacy | Maruthi Talkies

The Privacy Policy provided below is, with due respect to our use and protection of any personal information you provide to us through the maruthitalkies.com website.  
maruthi talkies media communications is the only owner of the website www.maruthitalkies.com and the policy is applicable to this site.

You may personally provide information which was reliable and related to you from several different points on our website. After accepting the policy at the time of your registration, you was approved and agreed to our collection,storage,use and disclosure of your personal information as described in the policy.

**Information Collection:**

With Pleasure, you can access or surf our website maruthitalkies.com for all kinds of news,updates which are related to the movie world. And You need to provide personal information for the registration or the access of certain services/webpage, if you intended to go for. maruthitalkies.com provides all the information which is real ,genuine and not copied content from any one. The information which you are surfing is purely from maruthitalkies.com. The information which you want to provide for registration are Name,Sex,Occupation, IP address,age ,etc…and other information, you need to provide to avail the services you seeked.

**Use:**

If you are interested or chosen to provide us the information, you would have agree, to use,transfer and the storage of info provided by you on our dedicated servers. The information provided by you shall not be sold/given/rented to third parties (third parties for this purpose do not include our group / holding / subsidiary companies and or our service partners / associates) for marketing purposes and other related activities without your prior consent.

The information provided by you would be utilised by us to:  
• Improve our website and enable us to provide you the most user-friendly experience which is safe, smooth and customized;  
• Improve and customize our services, content and other commercial /non – commercial features on the website;  
• Send you information on our products, services, special deals, promotions;  
• Send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so;  
• Resolve disputes, if any and troubleshooting;  
• Provide service updates and promotional offers related to our services/products.  
• Comply with any court judgment / decree / order / directive / legal & government authority /applicable law;  
• Investigate potential violations or applicable national & international laws;  
• Investigate deliberate damage to the website/services or its legitimate operation;  
• Detect, prevent, or otherwise address security and/or technical issues;  
• Respond to Claims of third parties;

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter your personal information we treat the data as an asset that must be protected and use tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security nor can we guarantee that third parties shall not unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and that other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that you provide. Therefore, although we work hard to protect your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**Links to Other Sites  
**  
The website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Maruthi Talkies Media Communications. Please be aware that we, Maruthi Talkies Media Communications and/or the website maruthitalkies.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  
We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.  
This privacy statement applies only to information collected by the website or to our other related websites provided it appears at the footer of the page therein. It does not apply to third party advertisements which appear on our websites and we suggest you read the privacy statements of such advertisers.

**Third-Party Advertising  
**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Opt-Out Cookie  
**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you.

**Changes in this Privacy Statemen** t

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and such other places we deem appropriate so that you are updated about the manner we collect information, what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

Any questions or clarifications with respect to this Policy can be sent to :[maruthi@maruthitalkies.com](mailto:maruthi@maruthitalkies.com)
